《神奇动物在哪里》
(盖勒特·格林德沃  黑巫师卷土重来肆虐欧洲)
(霍格沃茨魔法学校  加大安保力度)
(痛饮咯咯烈酒 歌声伴您欢)
(黑巫师恐怖威胁)
(巫师疑惑 足球就是麻鸡的魁地奇比赛吗)
(格林德沃袭击 加剧与麻鸡的战争威胁)
(神奇动物所有权在美国继续遭禁)
(魔法暴露威胁等级 创历年新高)
(反巫师情绪持续上升)
(皮奎里主席发声 请各方保持克制)
(麻鸡在五大湖徒步旅行时 受到沼泽挖子攻击)
(因伪造魔杖许可证 女巫师被起诉)
(麦克塔维 飞天扫帚)
(国际新闻 格林德沃在哪里)
(德文报纸 格林德沃在哪里 邪恶巫师仍然在逃)
(法文报纸 寻找格林德沃)
(我们是否安全 格林德沃散墦全球恐慌)
(伊丽莎白堡号)
杜戈尔 安静点儿吧 拜托了
Dougal, settle down now, please.
不会太久了
It won't be long.
下一位
Next.
- 英国人 - 是的
- British, huh? - Yes.
- 第一次来纽约 - 是的
- First trip to New York? - Yes.
里面有可食用的物品吗
Anything edible in there?
没有
No.
那家畜呢
Livestock?
得修修箱子了 没有
Must get that fixed. Um... No.
让我看一 下
Let me take a look.
(麻瓜模式)
欢迎来纽约
Welcome to New York.
谢谢
Thank you.
下一个
Next.
就好像一阵风
And it was like a... Like a wind.
又像一个鬼
Or like a... Like a ghost.
但很黑
But dark.
我还看见它眼睛了
And I saw its eyes.
亮晶晶的白眼睛
Shining white eyes.
一阵黑风有眼睛
A dark wind, with eyes?
像黑漆漆的一团
It's like a dark mass.
然后俯冲下来到 地下去了
And it dove down there. Down underground.
这件事应该有人来管管
Someone ought to do something about it.
这东西到处能看见 彻底失控了
It's everywhere, this thing. It's out of control.
问到什么了
Hey, you get anything?
一阵黑风 等等等等
Dark wind. Blah, blah.
像是某种大气乱流 要么电气问题
Some sorta atmospheric hooey. Or electrical.
去喝一杯
Hey, you thirsty?
不了 我在戒酒 向玛莎保证过不碰了
No. I'm on the wagon. Promised Martha I'd lay off.
是大气搞的鬼
It's atmospheric.
大伙让下 让我过去
Out of the way, folks. Coming through!
这座伟大的城市闪耀着人们智慧的结晶
This great city sparkles with the jewels of man's inventions.
放电影的戏院 机动汽车
Movie theaters, automobiles,
无线电 用电的灯
the wireless, electric lights,
- 眼花缭乱 像女巫对我们施了魔法 - 非常抱歉
- all dazzle and bewitch us. - I'm so sorry.
既然有光亮 就会有阴影 朋友们
But where there is light, there is shadow, friend.
潜藏在我们的城市里
Something is stalking our city,
伺机破坏 然后消失得无影无踪
wreaking destruction, and then disappearing without a trace!
我们必须战斗
We have to fight.
加入我们 第二塞勒姆 并肩作战
Join us, the Second Salemers, in our fight.
借过一下 宝贝儿 我就是想去银行
Excuse me, doll. Just trying to get to the bank.
我们必须共同战斗
We have to fight together
- 为了我们的 - 借过一下
- for the sake of our... - Excuse me...
抱歉 我的箱子
So sorry. My case.
不碍事儿
No harm done.
打扰了
Excuse me.
你
You!
朋友
Friend.
为何来参加我们的集会
What drew you to our meeting today?
我只是路过
Oh, I was just passing.
你是位找球手
Are you a seeker?
找求真相吗？
A seeker after truth?
实际我更像追球手
I'm more of a chaser, really.
听从我的箴言
Hear my words.
留心我的警告
And heed my warning.
有胆尽管嘲笑
And laugh if you dare.
巫师就在我们之中
Witches live among us.
我们必须共同战斗 为了我们的子孙后代
We have to fight together for the sake of our children.
为了我们的明天
For the sake of tomorrow.
那么你说呢 朋友
What do you say to that, friend?
抱歉 失陪
Excuse me.
需要效劳吗 先生
Can I help you, sir?
不 我还在等
No, I was just... I was just waiting.
嗨
Hi.
你来办什么业务
What brings you here?
跟您一样
Same as you.
你也贷款开面包店
You're here to get a loan to open up a bakery?
是的
Yes.
不会那么巧吧
What are the odds of that?
- 有实力的人胜出 希望是 - 抱歉 失陪
- Well, may the best man win, I guess. - Excuse me.
先生
Hey! Hey, mister!
Hey, mister.
伙计
Hey, fella.
科瓦尔斯基先生 宾利先生想现在见你
Mr. Kowalski, Mr. Bingley will see you now.
好的
Okay.
您目前在
You're currently working
罐头厂工作
in a canning factory.
眼下算是最好的了 我上一回还是在24年
That's the best I can do. I only got back in, uh, '24.
- 还是24年 - 是在欧洲 先生
- Got back? - From Europe, sir.
那会儿我还是美国远征军里的一名士兵
Yeah. I was part of the expeditionary forces there.
- 好吧 - 科瓦尔斯基先生
- All right. - Mr. Kowalski...
您得尝尝我做的甜滋滋 好吗
You gotta try the paczkis, okay?
我祖母的配方 里面的橙子馅儿 简直
It's my grandmother's recipe. The orange zest just...
科瓦尔斯基先生
Mr. Kowalski.
您想把什么抵押给银行
What do you propose to offer the bank as collateral?
做贷款的担保品
Collateral?
Collateral.
现在有了机器
There are machines now
一个小时里就能做几百个甜甜圈
that can produce hundreds of donuts an hour.
我知道 知道 但那种东西跟我的比不了 你
I know. I know. But they're nothing like what I can do. You...
银行要确保贷款不能有坏账 科瓦尔斯基先生
The bank must be protected, Mr. Kowalski.
祝您今天愉快
Good day to you.
英国先生
Hey! Mr. English Guy!
你的蛋要孵出来了
I think your egg is hatching.
怎么 刚才那是
What just happened?
不过 那打扰了
But, excuse me?
我刚才在那儿 在那儿
I was over there. Came over...
刚才在那儿
I was over there.
- 快跳进来 - 你好
- In you hop. - Hello?
不行
No.
大家都安静点儿 安静
Everyone settle down.
杜戈尔 可別逼我过来
Stay. Dougal, don't make me come in there.
别逼我下去
Don't make me come down there.
这可绝对不行
Absolutely not.
阿拉霍洞开
Alohomora.
原来你是打算偷钱
Oh, so you're gonna steal the money, huh?
统统石化
Petrificus Totalus.
宾利先生
Mr. Bingley!
科瓦尔斯基
Kowalski.
真要这样
Really?
不 別玩儿了
No. Don't play that.
看
Look.
別 不
Oh, no.
你看 別开枪
No, no, no. Don't... Don't shoot.
別开枪
Don't shoot!
好吧 最后一次 爱偷东西的讨厌鬼
Right. For the last time, you pilfering pest,
不是你的 爪子别抱着不放
paws off what doesn't belong to you.
有人在抢银行
Someone's robbing the bank!
对此万分抱歉
Awfully sorry about that.
是什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
您不需要有任何担心
Nothing that need concern you.
可现在不幸的是 你看到的实在太多了
Now, unfortunately, you have seen far too much.
如果不介意 请原地站好
If you wouldn't mind, if you just stand there,
只要一下就好
this'll be over in a jiffy.
那好吧
Mmm-hmm. Sure. Yeah.
对不起
Sorry.
麻烦了
Bugger.
你是谁
Who are you?
- 很抱歉 - 你是谁
- I'm sorry. - Who are you?
纽特·斯卡曼德 你又是谁
Newt Scamander. And you are?
你箱子里是什么东西
What's that thing in your case?
那是我的嗅嗅
That's my Niffler.
我说有什么东西在你
Say, you've got something on your...
看在德里弗伦斯·戴恩的份上 你把那东西放跑了
Why in the name of Deliverance Dane did you let that thing loose?
我不是故意的 它是屡教不改
I didn't mean to. He's incorrigible, you see.
要知道 只要亮闪闪的 它一定会…
Anything shiny, he's all over...
你不是故意的？
You didn't mean to?
- 不是 - 真会挑时候
- No. - You could not have chosen
偏偏在这时放跑了生物
a worse time to let that creature loose.
这儿现在是紧急状态
We're in the middle of a situation here.
我要把你带走
I'm taking you in.
要把我带去哪里
Taking me in where?
美国魔法国会
Magical Congress of the United States of America.
你为MACUSA工作
So you work for MACUSA.
做什么 算是调查员吗
What are you, some kind of investigator?
那麻鸡你处理妥当了吧
At least tell me you took care of the No-Maj.
- 那什么 - 那个麻鸡
- The what? - The No-Maj.
不通魔法 也不是巫师
No-Magic. The non-wizard!
抱歉 我们管他们叫麻瓜
Oh. Sorry, we call them Muggles.
他的记忆你抹掉了吧
You wiped his memory, right?
那个拎箱子的麻鸡
The No-Maj with the case?
- 呃 - 噢
- Um... - Oh...
第三章第一条 斯卡曼德先生
That's a Section 3-A, Mr. Scamander.
我要把你带走
I'm taking you in.
走吧
Come on.
抱歉 可我还有事要做 是真的
Sorry, but I do have things to do, actually.
那我看你要重新安排了
Well... You'll have to rearrange them.
你到纽约来做什么
What are you doin' in New York anyway?
我来买件生日礼物
I came to buy a birthday present.
难道不能在伦敦买吗
Couldn't you have done that in London?
不行 阿帕卢萨·马普弗断凯恩的饲养者
No, there's only one breeder of Appaloosa Puffskeins in the world,
世界上就一位 他恰好住在纽约 所以不行
and he lives in New York. So, no.
有人违反了第三章第一条
I got a Section 3-A.
嘿
Hey.
顺便告诉你 我们不允许在纽约饲养魔法生物
By the way, we don't allow the breeding of magical creatures in New York.
所以一年前就让那家伙关张了
We closed that guy down a year ago.
(魔法暴露威胁等级 严重无法解释的活动)
戈德斯坦恩
Hey, Goldstein.
瑞德
Hey, Red.
我们去重案调查司
Major Investigation Department.
- 我还以为你已经 - 我们去重案调查司
- I thought you was... - Major Investigation Department.
有人违反了第三章第一条
I got a Section 3-A.
(魔法骚乱 威胁暴露巫师界)
国际巫师联合会已威胁说要派代表团来
The International Confederation is threatening to send a delegation.
他们认为事件跟格林德沃在欧洲的袭击有关
They think this is related to Grindelwald's attacks in Europe.
我当时在场
I was there.
是魔法生物
This is a beast.
没有哪个人类有那种能力 主席阁下
No human could do what this thing is capable of, Madam President.
不管是什么 有一点可以肯定 必须阻止它
Whatever it is, one thing is clear. It must be stopped.
它会恐吓到麻鸡
It's terrorizing No-Majs.
只要麻鸡感到恐惧 就会攻击
And when No-Majs are afraid, they attack.
那就意味着暴露
This could mean exposure.
意味着可能的战争
It could mean war.
你的情况我说得很明确了 戈德斯坦恩女士
I made your position here quite clear, Ms. Goldstein.
是的 主席阁下 可我…
Yes, Madam President. But I...
你不再是正气师了
You're no longer an Auror.
不是了 主席阁下 可是
No, Madam President, but...
戈德斯坦恩
Goldstein.
这里出了一点小…
There's been a minor...
这间办公室现在只讨论
This office is currently concerned with
非常重大的突发事件 出去吧
very major incidents. Get out.
是 长官
Yes, ma'am.
拿到持魔杖许可了吗
So you got your wand permit?
所有来纽约的外国人都必须有
All foreigners have to have them in New York.
几星期前我就通过邮政方式申请了
I made a postal application weeks ago.
斯卡曼德…
Scamander...
那会儿你还在赤道几内亚
And you were just in Equatorial Guinea?
我才完成了为期一年的实地考察
And I've just completed a year in the fields.
我正在写一本书 是关于魔法生物的
I'm writing a book about magical creatures.
是那种灭绝生物指南
Like an extermination guide?
不是 我想写这本书帮助人们明白
No, a guide to help people understand
为什么应该保护这些生物 而不是杀死它们
why we should be protecting these creatures instead of killing them.
戈德斯坦恩
Goldstein?
她人呢
Where is she?
她人呢 戈德斯坦恩
Where is she? Goldstein?
戈德斯坦恩
Goldstein?
你是不是又去调查组管闲事了
Did you just butt in on the investigative team again?
你上哪儿去了
Where have you been?
什么
What?
她在哪儿抓着你的
Where'd she pick you up?
我？
Me?
你是不是又去跟踪第二塞勒姆了
Have you been tracking them Second Salemers again?
当然不是 长官
Of course not, sir.
下午好 格雷维斯先生 长官
Afternoon, Mr. Graves, sir.
下午好 阿伯内西
Afternoon, Abernathy.
格雷维斯先生 长官 这位是斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Graves, sir, this is Mr. Scamander.
他的箱子里有一个非常疯狂的生物
He has a crazy creature in that case,
逃出来并在银行大肆破坏
and it got out and caused mayhem in a bank.
让我看看小家伙
Let's see the little guy.
蒂娜
Tina.
对不起 祖母
I'm sorry, Grandma.
这是…
What the...
我妈妈 你妈妈
My momma, your momma
要去抓女巫
Gonna catch a witch
我妈妈 你妈妈 挥舞小棒子
My momma, your momma Flying on a switch
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫从不哭
My momma, your momma Witches never cry
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫必须死
My momma, your momma Witches gonna die
女巫第一号 溺死在河里
Witch number one, drown in the river
女巫第二号 让她上绞架
Witch number two, got a noose to give her
女巫第三号 看她被烧死
Witch number three, gonna watch her burn
女巫第四号 鞭子抽她转
Witch number four, flogging take a turn
收好传单 然后吃饭 孩子们
Collect your leaflets before you get food, children.
这是巫师的标记吗 女士
Is it a witch's mark, ma'am?
不是
No.
他没问题
He's okay.
真不敢相信你没对那人施消除咒
I can't believe you didn't Obliviate that man.
要是有人质询 我就完了
If there's an inquiry, I'm finished.
为什么是你完了 我才是那个…
Why would you be finished? I'm the one that's...
我本来不该接近第二赛勒姆的
I'm not supposed to go near the Second Salemers.
那是什么
What was that?
我猜是蛾子 大蛾子
Uh, moth, I think. Big moth.
都安静 我在给证人做笔录
Hey! Quiet down! I'm trying to get a statement.
我告诉你 又是一次煤气爆炸
I'm telling you, it's a gas explosion again.
我可不会带孩子回去 除非安全了
I ain't taking the kids back up there until it's safe.
抱歉 女士 可闻不到煤气味
Hey, sorry, ma'am. There ain't no smell of gas.
不是煤气 警官 我看见了
It weren't gas, officer. I seen it.
是一个庞大的 体型巨大的…
It was a gigantic, huge hippopoto...
煤气
Gas.
就是煤气 煤气
Gas. It was gas!
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander!
箱子打开过？
It was open?
就一条缝而已
Just a smidge.
那只疯狂的嗅嗅难道又逃出来了
That crazy Niffler thing's on the loose again?
可能吧
Uh... Might be.
那就找回来
Then look for it.
看啊
Look! Oh...
他脖子在流血
His neck's bleeding.
他受伤了
He's hurt.
醒醒 麻鸡先生
Oh... Wake up! Mr. No-Maj.
怜悯的刘易斯 那是什么
Mercy Lewis, what is that?
没什么可担心的
It's nothing to worry about.
是只莫特拉鼠
That is a Murtlap.
你那里面还有些什么
What else have you got in there?
- 是你？- 你好
- You? - Hello.
放松 先生
Easy, Mr...
科瓦尔斯基 我叫雅各布
Kowalski. Jacob.
不能给他施消除咒
You can't Obliviate him.
我们需要他当证人
We need him as a witness.
很抱歉 走了大半个纽约你一直朝我吼
I'm sorry. You've just yelled at me the length of New York
该早点施消除咒
for not doing it in the first place.
- 他受伤了 看起来不好 - 会好起来的
- He's hurt! He looks ill. - He'll be fine.
莫特拉鼠咬伤不会太严重
Murtlap bites aren't serious.
好吧 我承认比我见过的反应强烈一点
Yeah, I admit that is a slightly more severe reaction than I've seen.
可要是真的很严重 他就…
But if it was really serious, he'd have...
什么？
What?
第一个症状是肛门向外冒火花
Well, the first symptom would be flames out of his anus.
- 而他似乎没有 - 简直乱透顶了
- He doesn't seem to... - This is balled up!
最多也就持续48小时
It'll last 48 hours at the most.
- 我能把他留下 如果你愿意 - 留下他
- I can keep him, if you want me to. - Keep him?
他们不能留
We don't keep them.
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander,
你对巫师群体在美国的情况了解多少
do you know anything about the wizarding community in America?
有些事还是知道的
I do know a few things, actually.
我知道和不会魔法的人之间 你们的法律很落后
I know that you have rather backwards laws about relations with Non-Magic people.
下允许跟他们做朋友
That you're not meant to befriend them.
不能跟他们结婚 我觉得有些荒唐
That you can't marry them, which seems mildly absurd to me.
谁还会想要嫁给他
Who's gonna marry him?
你们俩都跟我走
You're both coming with me.
我不明白 我为什么要跟你走
I don't see why I need to come with you.
- 搭把手 - 我是在做梦 对吧
- Help me. - I'm dreaming, right?
- 没错 - 拜托了
- Yeah. - Please.
我累了 我根本没去银行
I'm tired. I never went to the bank.
一切都是场大噩梦 对吧
This is all just some big nightmare, right?
对你我都是 科瓦尔斯基先生
For the both of us, Mr. Kowalski.
(神奇魔法香水 利玛·卡丽萝)
嘿 你没事吧？
Hey, you all right there?
哇哦
Whoa!
这里就是新闻编辑部
And so this is the newsroom.
我们走
Let's go.
你们好吗
Hey, how are you?
给巴波一家让条道
Make way for the Barebones.
现在 他们只要把报纸放过去
Now, they're just putting the papers to bed,
就是这样
as they say.
肖先生 先生 他和参议员在一起
Mr. Shaw. Sir. He's with the Senator.
沒关系 巴克 我想见我父亲
Never mind that, Barker. I wanna see my father.
非常抱歉 肖先生 您儿子非要进来
I'm so sorry, Mr. Shaw, but your son insisted.
父亲你一定很想听听
Father, you're gonna wanna hear this.
我弄到了一个重大新闻
I've got something huge.
你哥哥和我正在忙着 朗登
Your brother and I are busy here, Langdon.
正在计划他的竞选活动
Working on his election campaign.
没时间听你说
We don't have time for this.
这位是玛丽·卢·巴波 来自新塞勒姆保护协会
This is Mary Lou Barebone from the New Salem Preservation Society.
她想告诉你一个惊天消息
And she's got a big story for you.
她有 消息？
Oh, she has, has she?
纽约市里到处都弥漫着奇怪的事情
There's strange things going on all over the city.
而事件背后的人 既不像你也不像我
The people behind this, they are not like you and me.
这就是巫术 没看出来吗
This is witchcraft. Don't you see?
- 朗登 - 她不是冲着钱来的
- Langdon. - She doesn't want any money.
要么她的故事毫无价值 要么她就是对要价撒了谎
Then either her story is worthless, or she's lying about the cost.
没人会免费透露有价值的东西 朗登
Nobody gives away anything valuable for free, Langdon.
您说的对 肖先生
You're right, Mr. Shaw.
我们想要的绝对比现金更有价值
What we desire is infinitely more valuable than money.
是您的影响力
It's your influence.
数百万的人阅读您的报纸
Millions of people read your newspapers,
而他们需要知道这一事件的危险性
and they need to be made aware about this danger.
地铁里出现了疯狂的乱流
The crazy disturbances in the subway.
看看这些照片
Just look at the pictures.
我更希望你和你的朋友离开
I'd like you and your friends to leave.
不 您会错失新闻良机 就看一眼证据
No. Look, you're missing a trick here. Just look at the evidence!
真的吗
Really?
朗登 听父亲的话 走吧
Langdon. Listen to Father and just go.
还有
And...
把这些怪物也一起带走
Take the freaks with you.
这是父亲的办公室 不是你的
This is Father's office, not yours.
我受够了 每次只要我进来
And I'm sick of this. Every time I walk in here...
行了 別说了
Okay. That's it!
谢谢
Thank you.
我们希望您会重新考虑 肖先生
We hope you'll reconsider, Mr. Shaw.
我们也并不难找
We're not difficult to find.
在那之前
Until then,
感谢您宝贵的时间
we thank you for your time.
小子
Hey, boy!
你掉了东西
You dropped something.
拿好了 怪物
Here you go, freak.
为什么不扔进垃圾桶 你们都属于那儿
Why don't you put that in the trash where you all belong?
这里右转
Take a right here.
进去之前
Before we go in...
我本来不该带男人回公寓的
I'm not supposed to have men on the premises.
既然这样 科瓦尔斯基先生和我
In that case, Mr. Kowalski and I
- 很容易就能找到其他住处 - 不 别这样
- can easily seek other accommodations. - No, you don't.
注意台阶
Watch your step.
是你吗 蒂娜
That you, Tina?
是我 埃斯伯斯托夫人
Yes, Mrs. Esposito.
就你一个人？
Are you alone?
我向来一个人 埃斯伯斯托夫人
I'm always alone, Mrs. Esposito.
哦
Oh...
蒂娜
Teenie,
你带男人回家了
you brought men home.
先生们 这是我妹妹
Gentlemen, this is my sister.
不想再穿点儿什么吗 奎恩妮
Wanna put something on, Queenie?
当然
Oh, sure.
那么他们是谁
So, who are they?
那位先生是斯卡曼德
That's Mr. Scamander.
他已经严重地触犯国家保密法了
He's committed a serious infraction of the National Statute of Secrecy.
他是犯罪分子？
He's a criminal? h.
这位是科瓦尔斯基先生 是个麻鸡
And that's Mr. Kowalski. He's a No-Maj.
他是麻鸡
A No-Maj?
蒂娜 你这是在干什么
Teen, what are you up to?
他病了 说来话长
He's sick. It's a long story.
斯卡曼德先生丟了点儿东西 我得帮他找出来
Mr. Scamander has lost something I'm going to help him find.
哦
Oh...
还是先坐下吧 亲爱的
You need to sit down, honey.
他这一天什么都没吃
He hasn't eaten anything all day.
而且…
And...
真是可怜
Oh, that's rough.
他没拿到贷款开他的烘培坊
He didn't get the money he wanted for his bakery.
你烤面包 亲爱的？
You bake, honey?
我喜欢做吃的
I love to cook.
- 你是一名摄神取念者 - 对呀
- You're a Legilimens? - Mmm. Yeah.
但碰到你们总有点麻烦 英国佬
But I always have trouble with your kind. Brits.
口音问题
It's the accent.
你知道怎么读人的想法
You know how to read minds?
別担心 亲爱的
Oh, don't worry, honey.
大部分男人跟你刚才想的一样
Most guys think what you was thinking
尤其是头一回见到我的
first time they see me.
现在你需要吃的
Now, you need food.
- 热狗 又吃啊 - 别读我的想法
- Hot dog? Again? - Don't read my mind.
午餐这么吃对健康非常不好
Not a very wholesome lunch.
斯卡曼德先生
Hey, Mr. Scamander.
喜欢派还是果馅卷
You prefer pie or strudel?
我并没有什么偏好
I really don't have a preference.
你喜欢果馅卷 亲爱的？
You prefer strudel, huh, honey?
那就果馅卷
Strudel it is.
坐吧 斯卡曼德先生
Well, sit down, Mr. Scamander.
我们不会给你下药的
We're not gonna poison you.
你很难过
You're upset.
又是你母亲
It's your mother again.
肯定有人又说了什么
Somebody said something.
他们怎么说的 告诉我
What did they say? Tell me.
你觉得我是个怪物吗
Do you think I'm a freak?
不 我觉得你是个非常特別的年轻人
No. I think you're a very special young man,
不然也不会叫你帮我 是不是
or I wouldn't have asked you to help me, now would I?
有什么新消息吗
Have you any news?
我还在找
I'm still looking.
接着说
Mmm.
格雷维斯先生 只要我知道 不管是女孩还是男孩
Mr. Graves, if I knew whether it was a girl or a boy...
我只看到那孩子有极其强大的力量
My vision showed only the child's immense power.
不论是男是女 都不超过十岁
He or she is no older than 10.
我看见那孩子离你母亲很近
I saw this child in close proximity to your mother.
你母亲我看的十分清晰
She I saw so plainly.
谁都有可能有几百个孩子
That could be any one of hundreds...
我还看见了別的 那些一直没告诉你
There's something else. Something I haven't told you.
我看见你跟我并肩站在一起 在纽约
I saw you beside me in New York.
只有你能得到这孩子的信任
You're the one who gains this child's trust.
你就是关键 我看见了
You are the key. I saw this.
你想加入巫师世界
You want to join the wizarding world.
而那些我也想要 克雷登斯
I want those things too, Credence.
都是为了你
I want them for you.
找到那个孩子
So find the child.
找到孩子 我们就都自由了
Find the child and we'll all be free.
工作一点儿不光鲜靓丽
The job ain't that glamorous.
差不多整天都在煮咖啡
I mean, I spend most days making coffee.
施魔法疏通盥洗室
Unjinxing the john.
蒂娜才是职业女性
Tina's the career girl.
不是 我们是孤儿
Nah, we're orphans.
爸爸妈妈得龙痘死了 那会儿我们还小
Ma and Pa died of Dragon Pox when we were kids.
哦
Oh.
你真贴心
You're sweet.
可我们互相照顾
But we got each other.
能不读我的想法吗 就一下
Could you stop reading my mind for a second?
哦
Oh...
请您別误会 我很喜欢
Don't get me wrong, I love it.
这顿饭简直好吃极了
This meal, it's insanely good.
我就干这个的 是个厨子
And this is what I do, I'm a cook.
是我这辈子吃过最好吃的了
And this is like the greatest meal I have ever had in my life.
你嘴真甜
Oh! You slay me.
我还从没跟麻鸡真正聊过天呢
I ain't never really talked to a No-Maj before.
呵
Huh.
真的吗
Really?
我没在戏弄他
I am not flirting.
我只是说 別用情太深了
I'm just saying, don't go getting attached.
他一定会被施消除咒的
He's gonna have to be Obliviated.
不是针对你
It's nothing personal.
没事吧 亲爱的
Oh, hey, you okay, honey?
戈德斯坦恩女士
So, Ms. Goldstein,
我想科瓦尔斯基先生今晚要早些休息
I think Mr. Kowalski could do with an early night.
而且你我明天早上也必须早起
Besides, you and I will need to be
去找我的嗅嗅 所以
up early tomorrow morning to find my Niffler, so...
嗅嗅是什么
What's a Niffler?
別问了
Don't ask.
在这边儿将就一晚
Hey, you guys can bunk in here.
我想你们会要杯热饮
Uh, I thought you might like a hot drink.
哇
Wow!
斯卡曼德先生 看 热可可
Psst! Hey. Mr. Scamander, look, cocoa.
洗手间在大厅右拐
Toilet's down the hall to the right.
谢谢
Thanks.
很感激
Very much.
快来
Come on.
看在爱的份上 天哪
For the love...
能坐下吗？
Will you sit down?
好主意
Good idea.
肯定是莫特拉鼠咬的
That's definitely the Murtlap.
你一定特別敏感
You must be particularly susceptible.
瞧 你是麻瓜
See, you're a Muggle,
我们的生理机能有点儿不一样
so our physiologies are subtly different.
- 不要动 - 啊…
- Stay still. - Ah...
这样应该不再出汗了
That should stop the sweating.
再吃这个 就不会抽搐了
And one of those should sort the twitch.
给 拿好
Here, take that.
再来点儿
Come on.
你拿的是什么
Whatcha got there?
这个当地人叫蝶翼妖
This, the locals call Swooping Evil.
听名字不太友善
Not the friendliest of names.
很灵活的小家伙
It's quite an agile fella.
我一直在研究它 我很肯定它的毒液
I've been studying him, and I'm pretty sure
相当有用 只要适当稀释
that his venom could be quite useful if properly diluted.
能去除那些不好的记忆
Just to remove bad memories, you know?
不过 最好別在这儿把它放出来
Probably shouldn't let him loose in here, though.
走吧
Come on.
快点儿 你快下来
Come on. Down you come.
来吧
Come on.
感谢帕拉瑟
Thank Paracelsus.
要是你跑出去 那真的是要天下大乱了
If you'd have got out, that could've been quite catastrophic.
它就是我来美国的原因
So he's the real reason I came to America.
带弗兰克回家
To bring Frank home.
等等 不 抱歉 別动
Wait. No, sorry. Stay there.
它对陌生人有那么一小点儿敏感
He's a wee bit sensitive to strangers.
好了 没事
Here you are. Here you are.
它是被贩卖出去的
He was trafficked, you see.
我在埃及找到它 浑身上下锁着铁链
I found him in Egypt. He was all chained up.
不能扔下它不管 一定得带它回来
Couldn't leave him there. I had to bring him back.
得把你送回去 你属于那儿 对吗 弗兰克
I'm gonna put you back where you belong, aren't I, Frank?
去到亚利桑那州的旷野荒原
To the wilds of Arizona.
好了 它们来了
All right, here they come.
谁要来了
Here who comes?
角驼兽
Graphorns.
- 嘿 - 別紧张
- Hey! - You're all right.
- 噢 - 你好
- Oh! - Hello.
你好
Hello.
它们是现存最后一对 还有繁育能力的
So they're the last breeding pair in existence.
如果我没办法救下它们
So if I hadn't managed to rescue them,
那么角驼兽就有可能永远消失了
that could've been the end of Graphorns forever.
好了
All right.
你在救助这些生物
What, you rescue these creatures?
对 正是这样 营救 养育 还要保护它们
Yes, that's right. Rescue, nurture and protect them.
我也在慢慢的教其他巫师去了解它们
And I'm gently trying to educate my fellow wizards about them.
跟我来
Come on.
哇
Wow.
泰特斯 芬恩
Titus, Finn.
波比 马尔洛 汤姆
Poppy, Marlow, Tom.
它患了伤风
He had a cold.
需要给身体保点暖
He needed some body warmth.
好了 快跳走吧
All right, on you hop.
它特別喜欢跟人腻在一起
He has some attachment issues.
好了 快去 皮克特
Now, come on, Pickett.
皮克特
Pickett.
不会 它们不会欺负你的 快过去吧
No, they're not gonna bully you, now come on.
皮克特
Pickett.
好吧
All right.
所以它们都怪我太宠它了
And that is exactly why they accuse me of favoritism.
杜戈尔不见了
Oh, no, Dougal's gone.
好吧 这就来
All right, I'm coming. I'm coming.
妈妈来了
Mum's here. Mum's here.
你们好
Oh, hello.
让我来看看你
Let me take a look at you.
我见过这些家伙
I know these guys.
你的鸟蛇
Your Occamy.
- 你说我的鸟蛇？- 没错
- What do you mean, my Occamy? - Yes.
你想不想…
Do you want to...
想啊 当然了
Oh... Oh, wow, yeah, sure.
好的
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
- 啊 - 抱歉 別那么摸它
- Ahh! - Oh, sorry, no, don't pet him.
它们很早就要学会保护自己
They, um, learn to defend themselves early.
你瞧 它们的蛋壳都是银的 所以是极其珍贵的
See, their shells are made of silver, so they're incredibly valuable.
好的
Okay.
它们的鸟巢很容易被猎人洗劫
Their nests tend to get ransacked by hunters.
谢谢
Thank you.
斯卡曼德先生？
Mr. Scamander?
叫我纽特吧
Oh, call me Newt.
纽特 我没觉得自己在做梦
Newt. I don't think I'm dreaming.
你怎么知道的
What gave it away?
我没那么好的脑子能想得出这些
I ain't got the brains to make this up.
我说你介不介意把这些小肉球
Would you mind throwing some of those pellets
扔给月痴兽 它们在那边
in with the Mooncalfs over there?
- 好 没问题 - 就在那边
- Yeah, sure. - Just over there's...
麻烦了
Bugger.
嗅嗅不见了
Niffler's gone.
当然会不见了 麻烦的小淘气
Course he has, little bugger.
只要有机会能抓着亮晶晶的东西
Any chance to get his hands on something shiny.
今天怎么样 雅各布
What did you do today, Jacob?
我在手提箱里呢
I was inside a suitcase.
嘿
Hey.
你们好啊
Oh, hello, fellas.
好了
All right. All right.
慢点儿
Take it easy. Take it easy.
小可爱
Cutie.
吃吧 吃吧
There it is.
退回去
Step back.
- 这东西是怎么回事 - 我说了退回去
- What's the matter with this? - I said, step away.
这到底是什么东西
What the hell is this thing?
那是默然兽
It's an Obscurus.
我这就得走了
I need to get going.
在它们受到伤害之前 全都找回来
Find everyone who's escaped, before they get hurt.
它们受到伤害？
Before they get hurt?
是的 科瓦尔斯基先生
Yes, Mr. Kowalski.
它们正处在一个完全不同的土地上
So they're currently in alien terrain
被数百万残忍生物所包围的星球上
surrounded by millions of the most vicious creatures on the planet.
人类生物
Humans.
那么你说 像那样中型大小的生物
So where would you say that a medium-sized creature
喜欢开阔的平原
who likes broad open plains,
树木 水洼 这类东西
trees, sort of waterholes, that sort of thing.
它会到哪儿去呢
Where might she go?
纽约市里吗
In New York City?
- 没错 - 平原？
- Yes. - Plains?
中央公园
Central Park.
那地方具体在哪里
And where is that exactly?
中央公园在哪儿
Where is Central Park?
你看
Well, look...
我很愿意带你去
I would come and show you,
可你不觉得这么做有点像两面派
but don't you think it's kind of a double-cross?
收留我们的姑娘们 还专门做了热可可
The girls take us in, they make us hot cocoa...
那你清楚 一旦她们看见
Now you do realize that once they see
你不再冒汗了 就会立刻对你施消除咒吗
that you stopped sweating, they will Obliviate you in a heartbeat?
小厨咒是什么
What's "Bliviate" mean?
就好像你醒过来 所有有关魔法的记忆都消失了
It'll be like you wake up and all memory of magic gone.
这些我全都不记得了吗
I won't remember any of this?
没错
No.
那好 对 好的 我帮你
All right, yeah, okay. I'll help you.
那就来吧
Come on, then.
克雷登斯 你上哪儿去了
Credence, where have you been?
我在找一个地方 为了明天的集会
I was looking for a place for tomorrow's meeting.
第32大街的转角 那里可以
There's a corner on 32nd Street that could...
对不起 妈妈
I'm sorry, Ma.
我也不知道怎么那么晚
I didn't realize it was so late.
- 吃饭的时候我一直在观察你 - 是啊
- I was watching you at dinner. - Yeah.
大家喜欢你 对吗 科瓦尔斯基先生
People like you, don't they, Mr. Kowalski?
那么我 我肯定大家也喜欢你
Well, I'm sure people like you, too, huh?
那倒沒有 不 我很惹人厌
Not really, no. I annoy people.
你为什么想当面包师
Why did you decide to be a baker?
好吧
Well, um...
因为感觉快死了
Because I'm dying
在那个罐头厂干活
in that canning factory.
每个人都快要死了
Everyone there's dying.
就好像把你的生命都压榨出来了
It just crushes the life out of you.
- 你喜欢罐头食品吗 - 不喜欢
- Do you like canned food? - No.
没错 我也是
Yeah, me neither.
所以才想自己做面包糕点 让大家高兴起来
That's why I wanna make pastries. You know, it makes people happy.
往这边走
We're going this way.
你拿到贷款了吗
So did you get your loan?
沒有
No.
我连个贷款担保品也没有
I ain't got no collateral.
在军队里待太久 这很显然 我也不清楚
Stayed in the army too long, apparently. I don't know.
你打过仗？
You fought in the war?
我当然打过仗了 每个人都打过
Of course I fought in the war. Everyone fought in the war.
你没入伍参战吗
You didn't fight in the war?
多数我都在跟火龙打交道
I worked mostly with dragons.
乌克兰铁肚皮
Ukrainian Ironbellies.
在东线战场
Eastern Front.
玻璃碎碎
Fenestra.
飞来飞去
Accio.
好了 高兴了？
All right. Happy?
逮住一个 还有两个
One down, two to go.
往那边儿跑了 警官
They went that way, officer.
手举起来
Hands up.
那到底是什么
What the hell is that?
狮子
Lion.
知道吗
You know,
纽约的确相当的有意思 比我想的有趣多了
New York is considerably more interesting than I'd expected.
把这个戴上
Put this on.
但是 我为什么要戴这种东西
But why would I have to wear something like this?
因为在极其强大的外力作用下
Because your skull is susceptible to breakage
你的头骨很容易被挤裂
under immense force.
可还给他们做了热可可
But we made 'em cocoa.
好的
All right.
给你 再把这个穿上
Here, you just, um, pop this on.
好吧
Okay.
这样你就绝对不需要再担心什么了
Now there's absolutely nothing for you to worry about.
告诉我 你让別人不要担心 那有谁信过你的话吗
Tell me, has anyone ever believed you when you told them not to worry?
我的人生观就是担心意味着要受两次罪
Well, my philosophy is that worrying means you suffer twice.
雌性正在发情
She's in season.
需要个伴儿
She needs to mate.
毒角兽的麝香 它会为之疯狂
Erumpent musk. She's mad for it.
好姑娘
Good girl.
来吧
Come on.
到箱子里来
Into the case.
走开
Get!
不
Oh, no.
修复如初
Reparo.
梅林的胡子
Merlin's beard!
树啊
Tree!
这两个一模一样
They're exactly the same.
都一样
Same thing.
纽特
Newt!
不 不要
No, don't.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
干得漂亮 科瓦尔斯基先生
Good show, Mr. Kowalski.
叫我雅各布吧
Call me Jacob.
好了 逮住两个 还剩一个
Well... Two down, one to go.
快跳进去吧
In you hop.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
今晚的这位主讲嘉宾
Tonight's keynote speaker
无需我再多做介绍
needs no introduction from me.
已经有人称呼他为未来的总统
He's been mentioned as a future president.
如果诸位不相信
And if you don't believe me,
就请读一读他父亲的报纸
just read his daddy's newspapers.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
我将为大家请出纽约市议员 亨利·肖
I give you the senator for New York, Henry Shaw.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢各位
的确
And it's true,
我们取得了一些进展
we have made some progress.
但是懒散不会有回报
But there is no reward for idleness.
就像那些酒气熏天的沙龙已经被禁止
So just as the odious saloons have been banished...
现在又是桌球室
So now the pool halls,
和那些私人会客厅
and these private parlors...
那是什么
What is that?
不 不
No! No!
是巫师
Witches.
我们的美国朋友竟然允许
Our American friends have permitted a breach
有人触犯国家保密法 威胁到暴露所有人
of the Statute of Secrecy that threatens to expose us all.
让盖勒特·格林德沃
I will not be lectured by the man
从他手里溜走的家伙没资格在这儿教训我
who let Gellert Grindelwald slip through his fingers.
主席阁下 非常抱歉打扰了 但情况紧急
Madam President, I'm sorry to interrupt, but this is critical...
你最好能有一个好理由
You better have an excellent excuse
这么闯进来 戈德斯坦恩女士
for this intrusion, Ms. Goldstein.
是的 我有
Yes. I do.
夫人
Ma'am,
昨天 有个巫师来到纽约 带了个箱子
yesterday a wizard entered New York with a case, this case,
这个箱子装满了魔法生物
full of magical creatures.
不幸的是 有些跑出来了
And unfortunately, some have escaped.
他是昨天到的
He arrived yesterday?
已经24小时了
You've known for 24 hours
一个沒有登记的巫师在纽约放跑了魔法生物
that an unregistered wizard set magical beasts loose in New York,
等有人被杀了 你才觉得该来告诉我们
and you see fit to tell us only when a man has been killed?
谁被杀了
Who's been killed?
那个巫师在哪儿
Where is this man?
斯卡曼德
Scamander?
你好 部长大人
Oh, hello, Minister.
西瑟斯·斯卡曼德？
Theseus Scamander?
那个战争英雄？
The war hero?
沒有 这是他的弟弟
No. This is his little brother.
你到纽约来干什么
And what are you doing in New York?
我来买一只阿帕卢萨马·普弗斯凯恩 大人
I came to buy an Appaloosa Puffskein, sir.
行了
Right.
你究竟来干什么
What are you really doing here?
戈德斯坦恩
Goldstein,
这位又是谁
who is this?
他是雅各布·科瓦尔斯基 主席阁下
This is Jacob Kowalski, Madam President.
他是麻鸡 被斯卡曼德先生的一个动物咬伤了
He's a No-Maj who got bitten by one of Mr. Scamander's creatures.
麻鸡？快施消除咒
No-Maj? Obliviate him.
对他施消除咒
Obliviate him.
梅林的胡子
Merlin's beard.
你清楚你的哪个生物该对此负责任吗
You know which of your creatures was responsible,
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander?
这不是动物干的
No creature did this.
请不要视而不见
Don't pretend.
你们肯定知道是什么 看看那伤
You must know what that was. Look at the marks.
那是默然兽
That was an Obscurus.
別太过分了 斯卡曼德先生
You go too far, Mr. Scamander.
美国根本就没有默然兽
There is no Obscurial in America.
没收那只皮箱 格雷维斯
Impound that case, Graves.
- 等等 別 还给我 - 逮捕他们
- Wait, no. Give that back. - Arrest them.
不要伤害那些生物
Don't hurt those creatures.
求你们了 你们并不明白 它们不会造成危害
Please. You don't understand. Nothing in there's dangerous.
- 它们不会 - 我们自然会有判断
- Nothing. - We'll be the judges of that.
送他们去牢房
Take them to the cells.
不要伤害那些生物 它们不会造成危害的
Don't hurt those creatures. Nothing in there is dangerous.
请別伤害我的生物 它们没有危险
Please don't hurt my creatures. They aren't dangerous!
求你们了 它们不会危害別人
Please! They're not dangerous!
它们不会危害別人
They're not dangerous!
我很抱歉 你的那些生物 斯卡曼德先生
I'm so sorry about your creatures, Mr. Scamander.
是真心的
I truly am.
劳驾谁能告诉我一下这个
Can someone please tell me
默然兽 默然兽是什么东西
what this Obscurial, Obscurius thing is, please?
已经几个世纪没出现过了
There hasn't been one for centuries.
三个月前我在苏丹见过一个
I met one in Sudan three months ago.
以前可能更多 现在也依然存在
There used to be more of them, but they still exist.
那时巫师还没有隐藏起来
It was before wizards went underground,
还在被麻瓜追杀迫害的时候
when we were still being hunted by Muggles.
年轻的男巫师和女巫师
Young wizards and witches
有时会去压抑自己的魔法力量
sometimes tried to suppress their magic
避免受到残害
to avoid persecution.
他们不但没有学习驾驭或控制自己的魔法力量
So, instead of learning to harness or to control their powers,
反而生出了一种叫默然兽的东西
they developed what was called an Obscurus.
是种不稳定 无法控制的黑暗力量
It's an unstable, uncontrollable dark force
突然爆发进行攻击
that busts out and attacks.
然后又消失无形
And then vanishes.
默然师的寿命并不长 是吗
Obscurials can't survive long, can they?
文献记载上还沒有
There's no documented
任何一宗默然师存活超过十岁的案例
case of an Obscurial surviving past the age of 10.
我在非洲见到的小女孩八岁
The one I met in Africa was 8 when she...
她死的时候才八岁
She was 8 when she died.
什么你们说的意思是
What are you telling me here?
肖参议员被杀 是孩子干的
That Senator Shaw was killed by a kid?
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫骑扫把
My momma, your momma Flying on a switch
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫从不哭
My momma, your momma Witches never cry
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫必须死
My momma, your momma Witches gonna die
女巫第一号 溺死在河里
Witch number one, drown in the river
女巫第二号 让她上绞架
Witch number two, got a noose...
把传单都发出去
Hand out your leaflets.
如果扔掉了 我肯定知道
I'll know if you dump them.
看见什么可疑情况要告诉我
Tell me if you see anything suspicious.
能结识你我真的很高兴 雅各布
It was good to make your acquaintance, Jacob.
衷心希望你的烘焙坊能开张
And I hope you get your bakery.
你这人挺有意思的 斯卡曼德先生
You're an interesting man, Mr. Scamander.
格雷维斯先生
Mr. Graves.
你被霍格沃茨赶出来 因为你危害到了人类的性命
You were thrown out of Hogwarts for endangering human life.
- 那是意外 - 牵扯到魔法生物
- That was an accident. - With a beast.
可是你的某位老师却对你百般辩护 不想开除你
Yet one of your teachers argued strongly against your expulsion.
那么
Now,
是什么原因让阿不思·邓布利多
what makes Albus Dumbledore
那么喜欢你
so fond of you?
我真的不清楚
I really couldn't say.
把一群危险的生物在这儿偷偷放出来
So setting a pack of dangerous creatures loose here was
不过是一个意外 是这样吗
just another accident. Is that right?
我为什么要故意这样做
Why would I do it deliberately?
想要巫师世界曝光
To expose wizardkind.
想挑起魔法和非魔法世界之间的战争
To provoke war between the magical and non-magical worlds.
为了更伟大的利益 大规模屠杀 你指这个
Mass slaughter for the greater good, you mean?
没错
Yes.
很对
Quite.
我不是格林德沃的狂热信徒 格雷维斯先生
I'm not one of Grindelwald's fanatics, Mr. Graves.
我很好奇 这个你想怎么跟我解释 斯卡曼德先生
I wonder what you can tell me about this, Mr. Scamander.
我这是一个默然兽
It's an Obscurus.
不是你想的那样
But it's not what you think.
是我想办法从苏丹小女孩儿身上分离出来的
I managed to separate it from the Sudanese girl
救那孩子的时候
as I tried to save her.
我想把它带回家仔细研究
So I wanted to take it home to study it.
可它在外面生存不了
But it cannot survive outside that.
它不会伤害任何人的 蒂娜
It could not hurt anyone, Tina.
没宿主就毫无用处了
So it's useless without the host?
没用？
Useless?
没用了？
就是因为那个魔法力量寄生蚕食 才杀死了一个孩子
That is a parasitical, magical force that killed a child.
这种东西你能用来干什么
What on earth would you use it for?
你谁也骗不了 斯卡曼德先生
You fool nobody, Mr. Scamander.
你把这个默然兽带到纽约市
You brought this Obscurus into the City of New York
就是希望挑起大规模冲突
in the hope of causing mass disruption,
大肆践踏保密法 让魔法世界暴露于众
breaking the Statute of Secrecy and revealing the magical world.
你知道它不会伤害任何人 你很清楚
You know that can't hurt anyone. You know that.
你犯下谋反之罪 背叛巫师群体
You are therefore guilty of a treasonous betrayal
因此将立即被判处死刑
of your fellow wizards and are sentenced to death.
戈德斯坦恩小姐 作为帮凶 罪犯同谋
Miss Goldstein, who has aided and abetted you...
不 这件事根本与她无关
No, she's done nothing of the kind.
她也被判处同样的刑罚
Receives the same sentence.
就立即执行
Just do it immediately.
- 我会亲自告知皮奎里主席阁下 - 蒂娜
- I will inform President Picquery myself. - Tina.
请吧
Please.
请別这样 博纳德特 求你了
Don't do this, Bernadette. Please.
不会疼的
It don't hurt.
蒂娜
Tina.
妈妈
Momma?
蒂娜
Tina.
快来 小南瓜 该睡觉了
Come on, pumpkin. Time for bed.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
是不是很美好
Don't that look good?
想进去吗
You wanna get in, huh?
山姆
Hey, Sam.
- 奎恩妮 - 他们让你到楼下去
- Hey, Queenie. - They need you downstairs.
我给这家伙施消除咒
I'll Obliviate this guy.
你没有资格
You ain't qualified.
山姆
Hey, Sam.
赛希莉知道你在和鲁比约会吗
Does Cecily know you been seeing Ruby?
- 你是怎么 - 让我来施消除咒
- How did you... - Let me Obliviate this guy,
赛希莉绝对不会从我这儿知道
and she'll never hear about it from me.
你这是干什么
What are you doing?
蒂恩有麻烦了 我在设法听情况
Hush. Teen's in trouble. I'm trying to listen.
雅各布 纽特的箱子在哪儿
Jacob, where's Newt's case?
我想那个叫格雷维斯的拿走了
I think that guy Graves took it.
好的 快走
Okay. Come on.
你不打算给我施消除咒
What, you're not gonna Obliviate me?
当然不会了 现在你是我们一伙的
Of course not. You're one of us now.
蒂娜
Tina.
没事了
It's okay.
阿拉霍洞开
Alohomora.
开门咒
Aberto.
他可能用很厉害的咒语锁住了办公室
He would know some fancy spell to lock his office.
好了 我们把美好的事物拿出来
Okay, let's get the good stuff outta you.
女巫
Witch!
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander!
不要惊慌
Don't panic.
那你建议该干什么
What do you suggest I do instead?
跳
Jump.
你疯了吧
Are you crazy?
跳到它身上
Jump on him.
蒂娜 听我说
Tina, listen to me.
我会抓住你
I'll catch you.
蒂娜
Tina.
我会抓住你的
I'll catch you.
能抓住你的 蒂娜
I've got you, Tina.
跳
Go!
来吧
Come on.
別管他的头了 走吧 快走
Leave his brains. Come on. Come on!
那是什么东西
What is that thing?
蝶翼妖
Swooping Evil.
好吧 我很喜欢
Well, I love it.
进去
Get in.
奎恩妮
Queenie!
这是要去哪儿
Where you going?
我…
I, uh...
我病了 阿伯内西先生
I'm sick, Mr. Abernathy.
又病了
Again?
箱子里是什么
Whatcha got there?
女士用品
Ladies' things.
您想看一看 我不介意
You wanna take a look? I don't mind.
天哪 不了
Good gravy. No. I, uh...
我祝你早日康复
You get well now.
谢谢
Thanks.
克雷登斯 找到那孩子了吗
Credence, have you found the child?
我不行
I can't.
给我看看
Show me.
好孩子 越快找到那孩子
My boy, the sooner we find this child,
你就能把所受的痛苦留在本该属于它们的地方
the sooner you can put that pain in the past where it belongs.
我要你带着这个 克雷登斯
I want you to have this, Credence.
我很少能这么信任人
I would trust very few with it.
非常少
Very few.
可你
But you...
不一样
You're different.
你找到那孩子 就碰一下这个符号
And when you find the child, you touch this symbol,
我就会知道 马上来找你
and I will know and I will come to you.
办成了 你将受到尊敬
Do this, and you will be honored
巫师都尊敬你 永远尊敬
among wizards forever.
这个孩子快死了 克雷登斯
The child is dying, Credence.
时间不多了
Time is running out.
你祖父养鸽子啊？
Your grandfather kept pigeons?
我祖父养描头鹰
Mine bred owls.
我以前很喜欢给它们喂食
I used to love feeding them.
格雷维斯总是强调 那些骚乱都是魔法动物所为
Graves always insisted the disturbances were caused by a beast.
得把你的动物都找回来
We need to catch all your creatures
那他就没法再拿动物当替罪羊了
so he can't keep using them as a scapegoat.
只剩一只没找着了
There's only one still missing.
杜戈尔 我的隐形兽
Dougal, my Demiguise.
杜戈尔
Dougal?
有个小问题是 我们看不见它
Slight problem is that, um, he's invisible.
- 看不见它 - 没错
- Invisible? - Yes.
大多数时候 它会…
Most of the time. He does, um...
- 那我们怎么才能抓 - 比登天还难
- How do you catch something... - With immense difficulty.
纳尔拉克
Gnarlak.
- 你说什么 - 纳尔拉克
- Excuse me? - Gnarlak.
我还是正气师那会儿 找他当过线人
He was an informant of mine when I was an Auror.
他以前买卖过魔法生物 副业那种
He used to trade in magical creatures on the side.
他不会恰巧有兴趣插手打听一下 是吗
He wouldn't happen to have an interest in paw prints, would he?
他对能卖的东西都有兴趣
He's interested in anything he can sell.
珍珠泪
Tears of pearl
火龙才匆匆抢下心爱好姑娘
When the dragon snapped up his best girl
比利威格虫忘记如何旋翼飞行
And the Billywig forgot to twirl
因为他的心上人离他而去
When his sweetheart left him cold
独角兽丟失了兽角
The unicorn done lost his horn
鹰头马…
And the hippogriff...
这样的小酒馆要怎么喝酒
How's a guy get a drink in this joint?
什么 你以前没见过家养小精灵
What? Ain't you ever seen a house-elf before?
哪里 当然见过了 我喜欢家养小精灵
Uh, no, of course I have. I love house-elves.
我叔叔就是家养小精灵
My uncle is a house-elf.
我看也是
Yeah.
六份忘忧水 一杯红耳 谢谢
Six shots of Gigglewater and a Lobe-Blaster, please.
所有麻鸡都像你这样
Are all No-Majs like you?
不 像我这样的只有我
No. I'm the only one like me.
这儿一半的人我都抓过
I've arrested half of the people in here.
你可以嫌我多管闲事
You can tell me to mind my business,
可我看见刚才在死亡药水池里
but I saw something in that death potion back there.
我看见你抱了那个第二赛勒姆男孩
I saw you hugging that Second Salem boy.
那男孩叫克雷登斯
His name's Credence.
他母亲总打他
His mother beats him.
他母亲收养了很多孩子 都会挨打
She beats all those kids she's adopted,
好像他母亲打他最多
but she seems to hate him the most.
他母亲就是你施咒攻击的麻鸡
And she was the No-Maj you attacked?
所以我弄丟了工作
That's how I lost my job.
他母亲举行集会 我就当着那群疯狂追随者的面
I went for her in front of a meeting of her crazy followers.
那些人都得施消除咒
They all had to be Obliviated.
成了一桩大丑闻
It was a big scandal.
他来了
It's him.
因为爱让所有人发狂
'Cause love drives all of us wild
那么
So...
你就是那个带了一箱子怪物的家伙
You're the guy with the case full of monsters, huh?
消息传的很快
News travels fast.
我希望你可以告诉我 任何能看见的
I was hoping you'd be able to tell me if there've been any sightings.
或是踪迹 诸如此类的
Tracks, that sort of thing.
你的脑袋现在可是值一大笔钱 斯卡曼德先生
You got a pretty big price on your head, Mr. Scamander.
为什么我要帮你
Why should I help you
而不是举报你呢
instead of turning you in?
我就当给你出个好价钱
I take it I'll have to make it worth your while.
还是当服务费吧
Um... Let's consider it a cover charge.
MACUSA出的可比这多多了
MACUSA's offering more than that.
望月鏡
Lunascope?
我有五个
I got five.
冻火灰蛇蛋
Frozen Ashwinder egg.
你看 现在我们
Oh, you see, now we're...
等一下
Wait a minute.
那是…
That's a...
护树罗锅
That's a Bowtruckle.
是吗
Right?
- 不行 - 別这样
- No. - Oh, come on.
它们能开锁 没说错吧
They pick locks, am I right?
不能把它给你
You're not having him.
行啊
Well...
祝你还能活着回来 斯卡曼德先生
Good luck getting back alive, Mr. Scamander,
MACUSA全体出动四处找你
what with the whole of MACUSA on your back.
好吧
All right.
皮克特
Pickett.
某种隐形的东西在第五大道附近大肆破坏
Something invisible's been wreaking havoc around 5th Avenue.
你也许想去梅西百货大楼看看
You may want to check out Macy's Department Store.
可能有你在找的东西
Might have what you're looking for.
杜戈尔
Dougal.
还有件事
One last thing.
MACUSA的那位格雷维斯先生
There's a Mr. Graves who works at MACUSA.
我想你是不是了解一些他的背景
I was wondering what you knew of his background.
你问的问题太多了 斯卡曼德先生
You ask a lot of questions, Mr. Scamander.
会招来杀身之祸的
That can get you killed.
MACUSA的人来了
MACUSA are comin'.
你居然向他们告密？
You tipped them off?
抱歉 纳尔拉克先生
Sorry, Mr. Gnarlak.
他让我想起了我的领班
He reminds me of my foreman.
你干什么 克雷登斯
Whatcha doin', Credence?
你在哪儿找到的
Where'd you get this?
还给我 克雷登斯
Give it back, Credence.
只是一个玩具
It's just a toy.
这是什么
What is this?
皮带给我
Take it off.
- 妈妈 - 我不是你妈妈
- Ma... - I am not your ma.
你妈妈
Your mother
是个邪恶的不正常的女人
was a wicked, unnatural woman.
那是我的
It was mine.
莫德斯迪
Modesty.
这是什么
What is this?
隐形兽基本上还是很和平的
Demiguise are fundamentally peaceful,
可要是着急了也会咬人
but they can give a nasty nip if provoked.
你们俩
You two,
去那边
head that way.
行事千万一定要出乎意料
And try very hard not to be predictable.
- 那个就是隐形兽 - 不
- Was that the Demiguise? - No.
但我想这可能就是为什么隐形兽会在这里
But I think it might be the reason that the Demiguise is here.
它可以洞察大概率事件
Its sight operates on probability,
它能预见到最有可能发生的近未来
so it can foresee the most likely immediate future.
它在干什么
What's it doing?
它在照顾小孩儿
He's babysitting.
你刚才说什么
What did you just say?
这是我的错
This is my fault.
还以为都在 我肯定是数漏一个
I thought I had them all but, uh, I must have miscounted.
它在照顾那东西
It was babysitting that?
鸟蛇能随意伸缩变大变小
Occamies are choranaptyxic.
所以它们会大到填满所有空间
So they grow to fill available space.
妈妈在这儿
Mummy's here.
需要一只昆虫
We need an insect!
只要是昆虫就行 还有茶壶
Any kind of insect and a teapot.
去找茶壶
Find a teapot!
不
Oh! No!
要抓住 我抓住了
I got it! I'll get it!
茶壶
Teapot!
蟑螂扔进茶壶
Roach in teapot.
随意伸缩
Choranaptyxic.
也能根据可用的空间进行缩小
They also shrink to fit the available space.
跟我说实话
Tell me the truth.
手提箱里跑出来的全都找着了
Was that everything that came out of the case?
全都找着了
That's everything.
而且这是实话
And that's the truth.
她来了
Here she comes.
回家高兴吗？
You happy to be home? Yeah.
是啊 我肯定你累坏了 老弟 来吧
Bet you're exhausted, buddy. Come on.
就把它放在那儿中间
Just place him in the middle there.
就这样
There you go. That's right.
沒错
Right.
我想我们该谈谈
I think we need to talk.
我不应该把你给他 皮克特
I wouldn't have let him keep you, Pickett.
我想我得把手砍掉 才能摆脱你
Think I would rather chop off my hand than get rid of you
尤其是你为我做了那么多 好了 别这样
after everything that you've done for me. Now, come on.
生闷气这事我想之前聊过 对吧
Think we've talked about the sulking before, haven't we?
皮克特
Pickett?
行了 对我笑下
Come on, give me a smile.
皮克特 对我…
Pickett, give me a...
好吧
All right.
你可真过分
Now that is beneath you.
纽特
Hey, Newt.
那女孩儿是谁
Who is she?
谁也不是
Oh, that's no one.
丽塔·勒斯特朗基
Leta Lestrange.
我听说过那个家族
I've heard of that family.
他们不是 你知道
Aren't they kind of, you know...
请不要读我的想法
Please don't read my mind.
抱歉 我说过请别这样
Sorry, I asked you not to.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
控制不了
I can't help it.
心受伤的时候更容易被读到想法
People are easiest to read when they're hurting.
我的心没伤
I'm not hurting.
是很久以前的事了
Anyway, it was a long time ago.
是你在学校里真正亲近的友谊
That was a real close friendship you had at school.
我们两个都不适合在学校待着
Neither of us really fitted in at school.
- 所以我们变得非常 - 非常亲密？
- So, we became quite... - You became real close?
那么多年
For years.
她是个索取者
She was a taker.
你需要一个给予者
You need a giver.
你们两个在谈什么
What are you two talking about?
没什么
Uh, nothing.
学校的事
School.
- 学校的事 - 你刚才…
- School. - Did...
你刚才说学校？
Did you say school?
难道还有学校
Is there a school?
还有一所巫师学校 就在美国？
A wizardry school here in, uh, America?
当然有 伊法魔尼
Of course. Ilvermorny.
它可是全世界最好的魔法学校
It's only the best wizard school in the whole world.
我想你会发现全世界最好的魔法学校 叫做霍格沃茨
I think you'll find that the best wizarding school in the world is Hogwarts.
胡说八道
Hogwash.
危险
Danger.
它感知到了危险
He senses danger.
默然师来过这里
The Obscurial was here.
小女孩去哪儿了
Where did she go?
帮帮我
Help me.
你不是说你还有个妹妹吗
Didn't you tell me you had another sister?
求你了帮帮我
Please, help me.
你那个妹妹在哪儿 克雷登斯
Where's your other sister, Credence?
我需要帮助
I need help.
小的那个 她在哪儿？
The little one. Where did she go?
求你了 就帮帮我
Please, just help me.
你妹妹现在非常危险
Your sister's in grave danger.
必须找到她
We need to find her.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
妈妈就是从这里领养了妹妹
Ma adopted Modesty out of here.
那家人有十二个孩子
From a family of 12.
她很想念兄弟姐妹 对他们念念不忘
She misses her brothers and sisters. She still talks about them.
她在哪里
Where is she?
我不知道
I don't know.
你这个爆竹 克雷登斯
You're a Squib, Credence.
我第一眼看到你 就应该察觉到
I could smell it off you the minute I met you.
什么
What?
你有拥有魔法的祖先 可你却没魔力
You have magical ancestry but no power.
可你说你会教我
But you said you could teach me.
你根本就学不会
You're unteachable.
你母亲死了
Your mother's dead.
就是给你的回报
That's your reward.
到此为止了
I'm done with you.
莫德斯迪
Modesty?
Modesty.
你不要害怕 别害怕
There's no need to be afraid.
我跟你哥哥一起来的 克雷登斯
I'm here with your brother, Credence.
你快出来吧
Out you come now.
克雷登斯
Credence.
的确该向你道歉
I owe you an apology.
我那么信任你
I trusted you.
以为你是我的朋友
I thought you were my friend.
我以为你不一样
I thought you were different.
你能控制它
You can control it.
克雷登斯
Credence.
可我并不想控制 格雷维斯先生
I don't think I want to, Mr. Graves.
(斯夸尔大楼)
天哪 那就是叫默然师的东西
Is that it? That's the Obscurial thing?
那比我听说过的任何一个默然师的力量都更强大
That's more powerful than any Obscurial I've ever heard of.
如果我回不来
If I don't come back,
照看好我的生物
look after my creatures.
需要知道的全都在这里面了
Everything that you need to know is in there.
什么？
What?
不能让他们杀它
They're not killing it.
纽特
Newt!
你也听到了 照顾好这些生物
You heard him. Look after them.
你一定拿好了 亲爱的
Keep hold of that, honey.
不 不行
No, no, no, no.
不能带你去
I can't take you.
- 求你了 让我去吧雅各布 - 嘿
- Please, let go of me, Jacob. - Hey. Hey.
是你说的 我们现在是一伙儿的
You're the one that said I was one of yous.
没错吧
Right?
可是太危险了
It's too dangerous.
有它在你身体里
To survive so long
还能存活那么久 克雷登斯
with this inside you, Credence,
是个奇迹
is a miracle.
你就是奇迹
You are a miracle.
跟我走吧
Come with me.
想想我们一起将取得何等成就
Think of what we could achieve together.
纽特
Newt!
是那个第二塞勒姆的男孩儿 他就是那个默然师
It's the Second Salem boy. He's the Obscurial.
可他不是小孩儿啊
He's not a child.
那男孩儿的力量一定很强 所以才有办法活下来
His power must be so strong he's somehow managed to survive.
纽特
Newt.
救那孩子
Save him.
格雷维斯先生
Mr. Graves.
蒂娜 你总是出现在别人最不想看见你的地方
Tina, you're always turning up where you're least wanted.
控制局势
Contain this.
我们一旦暴露 势必引发战争
Or we are exposed, and it'll mean war.
克雷登斯
Credence.
克雷登斯 我能帮你
Credence, I can help.
(市政厅站)
- 封锁这里 - 明白 长官
- Bar the area. - Yes, sir.
不许有任何人到下面去
I don't want anyone else down there.
克雷登斯
Credence...
你叫克雷登斯 对吗
It is Credence, isn't it?
我是来帮助你的 克雷登斯
I'm here to help you, Credence.
没想过要伤害你
I'm not here to hurt you.
我见过跟你情况一样的人 克雷登斯
I've met someone just like you, Credence.
一个女孩儿
A girl.
是个小女孩
A young girl
她被囚禁起来
who'd been imprisoned.
关在很远的地方 就因为拥有魔法受到惩罚
She had been locked away, and she'd been punished for her magic.
克雷登斯
Credence.
我能到你身边来吗
Can I come over to you?
我能过来吗
Can I come over?
那东西杀了我儿子
That thing killed my son.
我要司法正义
I want justice.
我一定会揭露你们的身份和你们的所作所为
I'll expose you for who you are and what you've done.
看看 快拍照片
Look! Take photos.
克雷登斯
Credence...
克雷登斯 別
Credence, no!
别这么做
Don't do this.
求你了
Please.
继续说吧 蒂娜
Keep talking, Tina.
继续跟他说话 他听你的
Keep talking to him. He'll listen to you.
他正在听你说
He's listening.
我知道那女人对你做过些什么
I know what that woman did to you.
我知道你受了很多苦
I know that you've suffered.
你不能再这样做了
You need to stop this now.
纽特和我会保护你的
Newt and I will protect you.
这个人
This man,
他在利用你
he's using you.
別听她的 克雷登斯
Don't listen to her, Credence.
我想让你获得自由
I want you to be free.
这没关系
It's all right.
就这样
That's it.
不要
Don't!
- 你们吓到他了 - 放下魔杖
- You'll frighten him! - Wands down!
谁敢动他 我就找谁算账
Anyone harms him, they answer to me.
- 克雷登斯 - 克雷登斯
- Credence. - Credence.
不
No!
克雷登斯
Credence.
一群蠢货
You fools.
知道你们刚才干了什么吗
Do you realize what you've done?
杀死默然师 是我授意的 格雷维斯先生
The Obscurial was killed on my orders, Mr. Graves.
是的
Yes.
历史也必将有所记载 主席阁下
And history will surely note that, Madam President.
今晚此地之事 无理无情
What was done here tonight was not right.
他该对一个麻鸡的死负责
He was responsible for the death of a No-Maj.
他还险些暴露了所有巫师
He risked the exposure of our community.
他更违反了我们最神圣的法律
He has broken one of our most sacred laws.
那法律让我们像委身于下水道的耗子
A law that has us scuttling like rats in the gutter.
那法律要我们隐藏真实的自我
A law that demands that we conceal our true nature.
那法律要让其管辖之人蜷缩在惧怕中
A law that directs those under its dominion to cower in fear,
唯恐我们会暴露身份
lest we risk discovery.
我问你 主席阁下
I ask you, Madam President,
我倒问问你们
I ask all of you...
这个法律要保护的是谁
Who does this law protect?
是我们
Us?
还是他们？
Or them?
我拒绝再屈从于它之下
I refuse to bow down any longer.
正气师们
Aurors,
我想你们可以解除格雷维斯先生手里的魔杖
I'd like you to relieve Mr. Graves of his wand
把他押回去
and escort him back...
飞来飞去
Accio!
显身
Revelio.
你以为自己能困住我
Do you think you can hold me?
我们会尽最大努力 格林德沃先生
We'll do our best, Mr. Grindelwald.
我们会死么 哪怕一点儿
Will we die just a little?
嘿
Hey.
我想有人应该看管着这东西
I figured somebody ought to keep an eye on this thing.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们欠你一个道歉 斯卡曼德先生
We owe you an apology, Mr. Scamander,
但是魔法世界已经暴露了
but the magical community is exposed.
我们也无法对整座城市施消除咒
We cannot Obliviate an entire city.
其实
Actually,
我想可以
I think we can.
本来是打算等到了亚利桑那州
I was intending to wait until we got to Arizona.
现在你是我们唯一的希望 弗兰克
But it seems that now you're our only hope, Frank.
我也会想你的
I'll miss you, too.
你知道该做什么
You know what you gotta do.
(时报广场惨遭损毁 魔法生物肆虐纽约)
(异常天气突袭纽约 罕见多雨十一月)
他们什么都不会记得
They won't remember anything.
那个毒液有非常强大的力量 能一忘皆空
That venom has incredibly powerful Obliviative properties.
我们亏欠你的太多了 斯卡曼德先生
We owe you a great debt, Mr. Scamander.
现在
Now,
让你的箱子离开纽约吧
get that case out of New York.
好的 主席阁下
Yes, Madam President.
那个麻鸡还在这里？
Is that No-Maj still here?
给他施消除咒
Obliviate him.
这不能有例外
There can be no exceptions.
很遗憾 即使是一个目击者
I'm sorry, but even one witness...
你们清楚法律
You know the law.
给你们时间告別
I'll let you say goodbye.
(地铁)
嘿
Hey.
对大家都好
This is for the best.
是啊 我本来…
Yeah. I was...
我本来就不应该在这里
I was never even supposed to be here.
我根本就不该知道
I was never supposed to know
这一切
any of this.
大家都明白 纽特带着我是因为
Everybody knows Newt only kept me around because...
嘿
Hey,
纽特 你为什么老带着我
Newt, why did you keep me around?
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
因为你是我朋友
Because you're my friend.
我永远不会忘记你对我的帮助 雅各布
And I'll never forget how you helped me, Jacob.
我跟你一起走
I'll come with you.
去別的地方 去任何地方
We'll go somewhere. We'll go anywhere.
你看
See,
我再也不会找到像你这样的了
I ain't never gonna find anyone like you.
我这样的人多得是
There's loads like me.
不
No.
你是独一无二的
There's only one like you.
我该走了
I gotta go.
雅各布
Jacob...
没事的 没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
不要紧
It's okay.
就像突然醒过来 对吧
It's just like waking up, right?
对不起 很抱歉
I'm so sorry. Sorry.
嘿
Hey!
亲爱的科瓦尔斯基先生
Dear Mr. Kowalski.
您在罐头厂里浪费才华
You are wasted in a canning factory.
请用这些鸟蛇蛋壳当担保品 贷款开烘培坊吧
Please take these Occamy eggshells as collateral for your bakery.
一位好心人敬上
A well-wisher.
其实…
Well...
- 已经 - 是吗
- It's been, um... - Hasn't it?
听我说 纽特
Listen, Newt, uh...
我想谢谢你
I wanted to thank you.
为什么谢我
What on earth for?
你心里很明白
Well, you know...
要不是你跟皮奎里主席说了那么多好话
If you hadn't said all those nice things to Madam Picquery about me,
我现在也不可能回到调查组
I wouldn't be back on the investigative team now.
我实在想不到还愿意让谁来调查我了
I can't think of anyone that I'd rather have investigating me.
还是努力別被人调查才好
Try not to need investigating for a bit.
我会的
I will.
接下来我的日子就很平静了
A quiet life for me from now on.
回到魔法部
Back to the Ministry.
把书的稿子投出去
Deliver my manuscript.
我很期待你的书
I'll look out for it.
神奇动物在哪里
Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them.
那位丽塔·勒斯特朗基喜欢看书吗
Does Leta Lestrange like to read?
谁？
Who?
那女孩 你一直带着她的照片
The girl whose picture you carry.
我真的不知道 丽塔现在喜欢什么
I don't really know what Leta likes these days.
因为人会变
'Cause people change.
- 是啊 - 我就变了
- Yes. - I've changed.
我这么觉得
I think. Uh...
也许就一点儿
Maybe a little.
要是你愿意 到时我给你寄一本
I'll send you a copy of my book, if I may.
我很愿意
I'd like that.
实在抱歉 那你觉得我是否可以当面把书给你
I'm so sorry. How would you feel if I gave you your copy in person?
我很愿意
I'd like that.
非常愿意
Very much.
(皇家辰星汽轮公司 果园街)
(科瓦尔斯基 甜蜜烘焙坊)
(品质烘焙 满意保证)
您的灵感是从哪儿来的 科瓦尔斯基先生
Where'd you get your ideas from, Mr. Kowalski?
不清楚 是真的
I don't know. I don't know.
都是突然出现的
They just come.
这是您的 別忘了这个
Here you go. Don't forget this.
请享用
Enjoy.
亨德利
Hey! Hendry.
去储藏室 行吗 谢啦 老弟
Storage, all right? Thanks, pal.